<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FlickPic</string>
    <string name="description">description</string>
    <string name="description2">description2</string>
    <string name="description3">description3</string>
    <string name="description4">description4</string>
    <string name="description5">description5</string>
    <string name="description6">description6</string>
    <string name="description7">description7</string>
    <string name="game_of_thrones_desc">Set on the fictional continents of Westeros and Essos, Game of Thrones
        has a large ensemble cast and follows several story arcs throughout the course of the show.
        The first major arc concerns the Iron Throne of the Seven Kingdoms of Westeros through
        a web of political conflicts among the noble families either vying to claim the throne or
        fighting for independence from whoever sits on it.</string>
    <string name="the_intruder_desc">A young married couple buy a beautiful house on several acres of land,
        only to find out that the man they bought it from refuses to let go of the property.</string>
    <string name="the_dark_knight_rises_bane_desc">Bane was the friend and protector of Talia al Ghul and the field
        commander of the League of Shadows. He was potent in both strategy and physical combat.
        He defeated the Batman in combat and manipulated the citizens of Gotham City with skilled
        oratory until Batmans recovery and return. He displayed his personality predominantly
        through expressions in his eyes. Banes physical appearance was defined by his mask, which
        inhibited the excruciating pain that agonized his body to bearable levels. He was portrayed
        by Tom Hardy in The Dark Knight Rises.</string>
    <string name="murder_on_the_orient_express_desc">A lavish trip through Europe quickly unfolds into a race against
        time to solve a murder aboard a train. When an avalanche stops the Orient Express dead in
        its tracks, the worlds greatest detective Hercule Poirot arrives to interrogate all
        passengers and search for clues before the killer can strike again.</string>
    <string name="mr_poppers_penguins_desc">Summaries. The life of a businessman begins to change after he
        inherits six penguins, and as he transforms his apartment into a winter wonderland, his
        professional side starts to unravel.</string>
    <string name="madeas_witness_protection_desc">It tells the story about Madea being a host to a family
        that the FBI has entered into the witness protection program due to the fact that the patriarch has been
        the CFO of a company that a crime family was using to further their Ponzi schemes.</string>
    <string name="horrible_bosses_desc">The plot follows three friends, played by Bateman, Day, and Sudeikis,
        who decide to murder their respective overbearing, abusive bosses, portrayed by Spacey,
        Aniston, and Farrell.</string>
    <string name="predators_desc">A group of elite warriors parachute into an unfamiliar jungle and
        are hunted by members of a merciless alien race. A group of elite warriors parachute into an
        unfamiliar jungle and are hunted by members of a merciless alien race.</string>
    <string name="moonlight_desc">A young African-American man grapples with his identity and sexuality
        while experiencing the everyday struggles of childhood, adolescence,
        and burgeoning adulthood.</string>
    <string name="pixels_desc">Combining animated video game characters and visual effects, the film
        involves an alien race misinterpreting video feeds of classic arcade games as a declaration
        of war, to which they respond by attacking Earth with technological replicas of
        characters from the games.</string>
    <string name="https_www_movieposters_com">Постеры предоставлены https://www.movieposters.com/</string>
    <string name="menu_title">Меню</string>
    <string name="watch_later_title">Смотреть позже</string>
    <string name="collections_title">Коллекции</string>
    <string name="settings_title">Настройки</string>
    <string name="favorite_title">Избранное</string>
    <string name="addToFavorite">Добавить в избранное</string>
    <string name="share">Поделиться</string>
    <string name="addFav">Добавить в избранное</string>
</resources>